<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>I think, therefore I am</title>
    <link>https://icode4passion.github.io/thegoodblog.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on I think, therefore I am</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 17:03:37 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://icode4passion.github.io/thegoodblog.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> Python Machine Learning Prediction with Flask </title>
      <link>https://icode4passion.github.io/thegoodblog.github.io/posts/ml_flaskapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 17:03:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icode4passion.github.io/thegoodblog.github.io/posts/ml_flaskapp/</guid>
      <description>Introduction As a python and machine learning enthusiast , i love reading blogs and code. In this article we will use Python and Flask in Deploying Machine Learning algorithms.
The main focus of the article will be how Flask/Python is used in deploying ML algorithms , we will not deep dive in to the Algorithms and their performance .
The take away from the article will be how dataset is fed to flask app and how are we sending the prediction back via jinja templete and what modules are encountered during the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://icode4passion.github.io/thegoodblog.github.io/posts/flaskmachinelearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 07:36:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icode4passion.github.io/thegoodblog.github.io/posts/flaskmachinelearning/</guid>
      <description>Brief Intro to Machine Learning Machine learning Machine learning (ML) is the study of computer algorithms that can improve automatically through experience and by the use of data. Reference: Wiki
Tools and Languages for Machine learning Python
 Easy to learn Languages Many Good Machine Learning libraries are available in python  Libraries in Python Numpy NumPy is the fundamental package for scientific computing in Python.Numpy
Pandas Pandas is an open source, BSD-licensed library providing high-performance, easy-to-use data structures and data analysis tools for the Python programming language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contacts</title>
      <link>https://icode4passion.github.io/thegoodblog.github.io/contacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 00:21:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icode4passion.github.io/thegoodblog.github.io/contacts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python SQL-Data Transfer to Text File </title>
      <link>https://icode4passion.github.io/thegoodblog.github.io/posts/posttwo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 22:50:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icode4passion.github.io/thegoodblog.github.io/posts/posttwo/</guid>
      <description>Now is better than never The “WHY” for writing this article is “Can an idea be molded into code when provided with proper tools and inspiration . This drove me to write simple python code and this article as well
As title suggest our main goal is to extract and transfer data from database to text file using python as a tool .There are lot of tools and methods that help us in achieving the above goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://icode4passion.github.io/thegoodblog.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 16:57:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icode4passion.github.io/thegoodblog.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://icode4passion.github.io/thegoodblog.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 16:31:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icode4passion.github.io/thegoodblog.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Guy who loves to code and enjoys every bit of life.
Philosophy in life is &amp;lsquo;I Think Therefore I Am&amp;rsquo; title of my blog coined by René Descartes (1596–1650) a French philosopher and mathematician.
Hope you enjoy my blogs. Thanks .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A P J Kalam -- an Inspiration...</title>
      <link>https://icode4passion.github.io/thegoodblog.github.io/posts/mypost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 01:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icode4passion.github.io/thegoodblog.github.io/posts/mypost/</guid>
      <description>Where there is righteousness in the heart, there is beauty in the character. When there is beauty in the character, there is harmony in the home. When there is harmony in the home, there is order in the nation. When there is order in the nation, there is peace in the world. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
